A Guide to the Asia Society Exhibition files FA258
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Sculptural Jades of China
  - Installation, undated (Box 104, Folder 856)
  - Lectures, 1970 (Box 104, Folder 857)
  - Loan Forms, 1970-1971 (Box 104, Folder 858)
  - Loan Lists, 1970 (Box 104, Folder 859)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 104, Folder 860)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1970 (Box 104, Folder 861)
  - Photos, 1971 (Box 104, Folder 862)
  - Photos, undated (Box 104, Folder 863)
  - Photos, undated (Box 104, Folder 864)
  - Photos, undated (Box 105, Folder 865)
  - Photos: Not in Show, undated (Box 105, Folder 866)
- The Sculpture of Thailand, Exhibited: 1972 October-December
  The Exhibition, presented under the patronage of His Majesty King Bhūmibok Adulyadej and Her Majesty Queen Sirikit of Thailand, was organized by Professor Theodore Bowie of Indiana University. Prince Subhadradis Diskul, Dean of the Faculty of Archaelogy, Silpakorn University, Bangkok, Thailand, wrote the descriptive entries for the catalogue. Alexander B. Griswold contributed both a learned article to the catalogue as well as notes on the catalogue and plates. The Exhibition traveled to several cities, including Cleveland, Ohio, Bloomington, Indiana, Montreal, Canada, Seattle, Washington, and Dallas, Texas, after it appeared at the Asia House Gallery.
  - Acoustiguide Script, undated (Box 106, Folder 881)
  - "Arts of Thailand": 1960 Exhibition, 1959, 1962 (Box 106, Folder 882)
  - Bills Paid, 1973-1974 (Box 106, Folder 883)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1971-1976 (Box 106, Folder 884)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1968, 1970-1975 (Box 106, Folder 885)
  - Catalogue: Original Manuscript, 1971 (Box 106, Folder 886)
  - Circulation of Exhibition, 1970-1974 (Box 107, Folder 887)
  - Circulation of Exhibition: Australia, 1972-1973 (Box 107, Folder 888)
  - Circulation of Exhibition: Cleveland, 1970-1973 (Box 107, Folder 889)
  - Circulation of Exhibition: Dallas, 1971, 1973-1974 (Box 107, Folder 890)
  - Circulation of Exhibition: Honolulu, 1972-1974 (Box 107, Folder 891)
  - Circulation of Exhibition: Indiana, 1971-1973 (Box 107, Folder 892)
  - Circulation of Exhibition: Montreal, 1971-1974 (Box 107, Folder 893)
  - Circulation of Exhibition: Seattle, 1970-1973 (Box 107, Folder 894)
  - Contract, 1970-1971 (Box 107, Folder 895)
  - Contract, 1972 (Box 107, Folder 896)
  - Correspondence: Theodore Bowie, 1967, 1969-1973 (Box 108, Folder 897)
  - Correspondence: Danish Assistance (Inactive), 1969-1970 (Box 108, Folder 898)
  - Correspondence: Domestic, 1969-1974 (Box 108, Folder 899)
  - Correspondence: Foreign, 1969-1974, 1976 (Box 108, Folder 900)
  - Correspondence: Elizabeth Lyons, 1970-1972, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 901)
  - Correspondence: National Endowment for the Arts, 1971, 1973 (Box 108, Folder 902)
  - Curators, 1972-1974 (Box 108, Folder 903)
  - Daily Reports, 1972 (Box 108, Folder 904)
  - Damages, 1972-1974 (Box 109, Folder 905)
  - Financial, 1969-1972, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 906)
  - Identification Photos 1-42, undated (Box 109, Folder 907)
  - Identification Photos 43-84, undated (Box 109, Folder 908)
  - Installation, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 909)
  - Installation: Instructions, undated (Box 110, Folder 910)
  - Installation: Photos, 1972 (Box 110, Folder 911)
  - Insurance, 1970-1974 (Box 110, Folder 912)
  - Lectures, 1972 (Box 110, Folder 913)
  - Loan Lists, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 914)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1970-1972 (Box 110, Folder 915)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1973-1974 (Box 110, Folder 916)
  - Packing Lists, 1972 (Box 110, Folder 917)
  - Preview and Opening, 1972-1973 (Box 111, Folder 918)
  - Publicity, 1972-1974 (Box 111, Folder 919)
  - Publicity A-Z, 1972-1973 (Box 111, Folder 920)
  - Publicity: Press Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 111, Folder 921)
  - Thai Painting, 1960 (Box 111, Folder 922)
  - Visit of Prince Subhadradis Diskul, 1972 (Box 111, Folder 923)
  - Washburn Trip to Asia, 1967,1970 (Box 111, Folder 924)
- Ceramic Art of Japan: One Hundred Masterpieces from Japanese Collections, Exhibited: 1973 January-March
  The Exhibition of 100 masterpieces from Japanese collections was organized by Henry Trubner, Curator of Asiatic Art at the Seattle Art Museum, Washington. Following its showing in Seattle, the Exhibition was circulated to several other museums. At Asia House, it was presented in two sections: January 18-February 11 and February 14-March 11. The catalogue for the Exhibition was written and prepared by Mr. Trubner.
  - Acoustiguide Scripts, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 925)
  - Catalogue, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 926)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1971-1972 (Box 112, Folder 927)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 112, Folder 928)
  - Contract, 1971-1972 (Box 112, Folder 929)
  - Correspondence: Domestic, 1972-1973 (Box 112, Folder 930)
  - Correspondence: Foreign, 1972-1973 (Box 112, Folder 931)
  - Correspondence: Henry Trubner, 1969-1973 (Box 112, Folder 932)
  - Curators, 1972-1973 (Box 112, Folder 933)
  - Daily Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 112, Folder 934)
  - Financial, 1972-1973 (Box 112, Folder 935)
  - Installation, 1972 (Box 112, Folder 936)
  - International Symposium on Japanese Ceramics, Seattle Art Museum, 1972 September (Box 112, Folder 937)
  - Lectures, 1972-1973 (Box 112, Folder 938)
  - Opening, 1972-1973 (Box 112, Folder 939)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1972-1973 (Box 113, Folder 940)
  - Photos: Negatives, undated (Box 113, Folder 941)
  - Publicity, 1972-1973 (Box 113, Folder 942)
  - Publicity: Press Clippings, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 943)
  - Publicity: Seattle Art Museum, 1972-1973 (Box 113, Folder 944)
- A Flower From Every Meadow: Indian Paintings from American Collections, Exhibited: 1973 April-June
  The works in the Exhibition were chosen by Stuart Cary Welch, Lecturer in the Arts, Harvard University, Cambridge, Massachusetts. Mr. Welch also authored the catalogue. Following its showing at Asia House, the Exhibition was shown at the Center for Asian Art and Culture (Brundage Collection), San Francisco, California, and the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, Buffalo, New York.
  - Acoustiguide Script, Final, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 945)
  - Acoustiguide Script, Second Draft, 1973 (Box 113, Folder 946)
  - Bills Paid, 1973-1974 (Box 113, Folder 947)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1972-1974 (Box 113, Folder 948)
  - Catalogue: Color Proofs, undated (Box 113, Folder 949)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 113, Folder 950)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript, Original, 1972 (Box 114, Folder 951)
  - Catalogue: Original Manuscript, 1972 (Box 114, Folder 952)
  - Circulation of Exhibition, 1971-1972 (Box 114, Folder 953)
  - Circulation of Exhibition: Buffalo - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1972-1973 (Box 114, Folder 954)
  - Circulation of Exhibition: San Francisco - Avery Brundage Collection, 1972-1973 (Box 114, Folder 955)
  - Copy Negatives, undated (Box 114, Folder 956)
  - Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 114, Folder 957)
  - Correspondence: Stuart Cary Welch, 1971-1973, 1976 (Box 114, Folder 958)
  - Correspondence with Lenders, 1971-1975 (Box 115, Folder 959)
  - Daily Reports, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 960)
  - Exhibition Data, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 961)
  - Financing, 1971-1973 (Box 115, Folder 962)
  - Installation, 1972-1973 (Box 115, Folder 963)
  - Insurance, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 964)
  - Lectures, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 965)
  - Lists, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 966)
  - Loan Agreements, 1972-1974 (Box 115, Folder 967)
  - Loan Lists, 1972 (Box 115, Folder 968)
  - Loans Refused or Withdrawn, 1972 (Box 115, Folder 969)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1971-1974 (Box 115, Folder 970)
  - Opening, 1972-1973 (Box 115, Folder 971)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1972-1974 (Box 116, Folder 972)
  - Poster, 1972-1974 (Box 116, Folder 973)
  - Publicity, 1972-1975 (Box 116, Folder 974)
  - Publicity: Press Clippings, 1973, 1975 (Box 116, Folder 975)
- Shah 'Abbas and the Arts of Isfahan, Exhibited: 1973 October-December
  The Exhibition was a joint effort of The Asia Society and Harvard University's Fogg Museum, Cambridge, Massachusetts. The works in the Exhibition were selected by Anthony Welch of the University of Victoria, Victoria, British Colombia, Canada. Professor Welch wrote the catalogue for the Exhibition.
  - Acoustiguide: Correspondence, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 976)
  - Acoustiguide: Script, undated (Box 116, Folder 977)
  - Bills Paid, 1973-1974 (Box 116, Folder 978)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1972-1974 (Box 117, Folder 979)
  - Catalogue: Copy of Manuscript Sent to Printer, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 980)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 117, Folder 981)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript Sent to Printer, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 982)
  - Catalogue: Original Manuscript, 1972-1973 (Box 117, Folder 983)
  - Catalogue: Proofs, Author's, undated (Box 118, Folder 984)
  - Correspondence: Domestic, 1970-1975 (Box 118, Folder 985)
  - Correspondence: Fogg Art Museum, 1971-1975 (Box 118, Folder 986)
  - Correspondence: Anthony Welch, 1970, 1972 (Box 118, Folder 987)
  - Correspondence: Anthony Welch, 1973-1974, 1976 (Box 118, Folder 988)
  - Correspondence with Lenders, A-M, 1972-1974 (Box 118, Folder 989)
  - Correspondence with Lenders, N-Z, 1972-1974 (Box 118, Folder 990)
  - Daily Reports, 1973 (Box 118, Folder 991)
  - Film, 1971-1973, 1975 (Box 119, Folder 992)
  - Financing, 1972-1976 (Box 119, Folder 993)
  - Installation, 1972-1974 (Box 119, Folder 994)
  - Insurance, 1973-1974 (Box 119, Folder 995)
  - Lectures, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 996)
  - Loan Agreements, A-M, 1972-1974 (Box 119, Folder 997)
  - Loan Agreements, N-Z, 1972-1973 (Box 119, Folder 998)
  - Loan Lists, 1972-1973 (Box 119, Folder 999)
  - Loan Receipts, 1973 (Box 119, Folder 1000)
  - Loans Refused or Withdrawn, 1972 (Box 119, Folder 1001)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Grant Application, 1972-1974 (Box 120, Folder 1002)
  - Opening, 1973-1974 (Box 120, Folder 1003)
  - Packing and Shippping, 1973 (Box 120, Folder 1004)
  - Publicity, 1973-1974 (Box 120, Folder 1005)
  - Slides, 1974 (Box 120, Folder 1006)
- The Colors of Ink: Chinese Paintings and Related Ceramics from the Cleveland Museum of Art, Exhibited: 1974 January-March
  The Exhibition featured works from the Cleveland Museum's collection, chosen for display at Asia House by Serman E. Lee, Director of the Museum. Dr. Lee also authored the catalogue.
  - Acoustiguide Script, undated (Box 120, Folder 1007)
  - Bills Paid, 1973-1974 (Box 120, Folder 1008)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1973-1974 (Box 120, Folder 1009)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 120, Folder 1010)
  - Catalogue: Master Galleys, undated (Box 121, Folder 1011)
  - Catalogue: Original Manuscript, undated (Box 121, Folder 1012)
  - Catalogue: Setting Copy, undated (Box 121, Folder 1013)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 121, Folder 1014)
  - Daily Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 121, Folder 1015)
  - Financing, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 1016)
  - Installation, 1973-1974 (Box 121, Folder 1017)
  - Insurance, 1973-1974 (Box 121, Folder 1018)
  - Lectures, 1973-1974 (Box 121, Folder 1019)
  - Lists, 1973 (Box 121, Folder 1020)
  - Loan Record Sheets, 1974 (Box 122, Folder 1021)
  - Opening, 1973-1974 (Box 122, Folder 1022)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1973-1974 (Box 122, Folder 1023)
  - Publicity, 1973-1975 (Box 122, Folder 1024)
  - Publicity: Press Clippings, 1974 (Box 122, Folder 1025)
- Rājāsthānī Temple Hangings of the Kŗishņa Cult, Exhibited: 1974 April-June
  The Exhibition from the collection of Karl Mann was organized by the American Federation of Arts. The catalogue for the Exhibition was authored by Robert Skelton of the Victoria and Albert Museum in London and was available through the American Federation of Arts.
  - Acoustiguide: Correspondence, undated (Box 122, Folder 1026)
  - Bills Paid, 1973-1974 (Box 122, Folder 1027)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 1028)
  - Contract, 1972 (Box 122, Folder 1029)
  - Correspondence: Domestic, 1972-1974 (Box 122, Folder 1030)
  - Correspondence: Saryu Doshi, 1973-1974 (Box 122, Folder 1031)
  - Correspondence: Foreign, 1972-1974 (Box 122, Folder 1032)
  - Correspondence with Lenders, 1973-1974 (Box 122, Folder 1033)
  - Daily Reports, 1974 (Box 122, Folder 1034)
  - Financing/Budget, 1972-1974, 1976 (Box 122, Folder 1035)
  - Installation, 1972-1974 (Box 123, Folder 1036)
  - Lectures, 1974 (Box 123, Folder 1037)
  - Lists, undated (Box 123, Folder 1038)
  - Loan Agreements, 1974 (Box 123, Folder 1039)
  - Loans Refused or Withdrawn, 1973 (Box 123, Folder 1040)
  - Opening and Private Preview, 1973-1974 (Box 123, Folder 1041)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1973-1974 (Box 123, Folder 1042)
  - Photographs: Altar, undated (Box 123, Folder 1043)
  - Photographs: Labels, undated (Box 123, Folder 1044)
  - Publicity, 1973-1974 (Box 123, Folder 1045)
  - Publicity: Press Clippings, 1974 (Box 123, Folder 1046)
- The Poet-Painters: Buson and His Followers, Exhibited: 1974 October-December
  The Exhibition was organized by Calvin French of the University of Michigan Department of the History of Art.
  - Bills Paid, 1974 (Box 123, Folder 1047)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1973-1974 (Box 123, Folder 1048)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 123, Folder 1049)
  - Condition Report, 1974 (Box 123, Folder 1050)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 123, Folder 1051)
  - Correspondence: University of Michigan, 1973-1975 (Box 123, Folder 1052)
  - Daily Reports, 1974 (Box 123, Folder 1053)
  - Financing/Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 124, Folder 1054)
  - Guest Book, 1974 (Box 124, Folder 1055)
  - Installation, 1973-1974 (Box 124, Folder 1056)
  - Insurance, 1973-1975 (Box 124, Folder 1057)
  - Lectures, 1974 (Box 124, Folder 1058)
  - Lists, undated (Box 124, Folder 1059)
  - Loan Agreements, undated (Box 124, Folder 1060)
  - Opening and Private Preview, 1974 (Box 124, Folder 1061)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1974-1975 (Box 124, Folder 1062)
  - Photographs: Labels, undated (Box 124, Folder 1063)
  - Publicity, 1974-1975 (Box 124, Folder 1064)
  - Publicity: Press Clippings, 1974 (Box 124, Folder 1065)
- Asian Art: Part II: Selections from the Collection of Mr. and Mrs. John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Exhibited: 1975 January-March
  The Exhibition of 70 pieces was chosen by Sherman E. Lee, Director of the Cleveland Museum of Art. Dr. Lee also authored the catalogue for the Exhibition.
  - Acoustiguide, 1974 (Box 124, Folder 1066)
  - Bills Paid, 1974-1975 (Box 124, Folder 1067)
  - Catalogue: Annotated, 1975 (Box 124, Folder 1068)
  - Catalogue: Business Arrangements, 1974-1975 (Box 124, Folder 1069)
  - Catalogue: Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 124, Folder 1070)
  - Catalogue: Manuscript Sent to Printer, undated (Box 124, Folder 1071)
  - Catalogue: Original Manuscript, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 1072)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1073)
  - Correspondence: Sherman E. Lee, 1974-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1074)
  - Correspondence: Rockefellers, 1974-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1075)
  - Daily Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1076)
  - Financing/Budget, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 1077)
  - Guest Book, 1975 (Box 125, Folder 1078)
  - Installation, 1974-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1079)
  - Lectures, 1974-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1080)
  - Lists, undated (Box 125, Folder 1081)
  - Loan Agreements, 1974-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1082)
  - Opening and Private Preview, 1974-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1083)
  - Packing and Shipping, 1974-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1084)
  - Publicity, 1974-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1085)
  - Publicity: Press Clippings, 1974-1975 (Box 125, Folder 1086)